Hey, man. Uh, thank you guys for having
me. You know, very excited to be up
here. Um, they're just getting a high
energy dog, man. And that's that's what
I want to bring, you know, to this team
and this offense. I love the culture
here. I feel like I'll fit in, you know,
perfectly. Um, just a dog. That's that's
all I can say. Complete dog.
>> Where do you I'm sorry. Where do you
feel you've grown most as the tight end
that you can that you can take here and
build on your game with? Uh, I'll say uh
my playmaking ability over the years.
Just when I get the ball in my hands,
just always um going to make a play. I
feel like that's been the number one
thing that I've been improved on my past
couple years in the league, just showing
that big playability and just super
excited to get more opportunities here
and just be able to do that for the
team.
>> Thank you, Nikki.
>> Hi, Jake. Um, having played at Maryland,
how much did it mean more to you to sign
here? Oh, definitely. Um, it was
definitely a um a factor for me just
coming back coming back here, you know,
where I went to school. It was awesome.
I know the area. Uh, I know the team. I
think this was actually the first
stadium I've ever played my my first
college game into. So, that was pretty
cool. Uh, yeah.
>> And you've forced a lot of missed
tackles over the years. Is that
something you take pride in? Is that um
a part of your game that you believe is
as a forte?
>> Yeah, I think that's the number one part
of my game. And like John said, where do
they where are we getting to me? And I
said, a dog. And that's just a part of
that. You see those force missed
tackles, you know, stuff like that.
That's that's what I pride myself on,
you know, in football, being a guy that
that doesn't let the the just one guy
take them down. Um, that's how I want to
play the game. That's how I know how to
play the game, and that's just me.
>> Scott,
>> what's up, Jake? Welcome back to the
DMV, my friend.
>> Hey, thank you, man. I appreciate you.
>> Uh, you get to you get a chance now to
play with Jaden Daniels. Obviously, a
very good quarterback. Uh, how appealing
was that to come to Washington knowing
you get Jaden throwing you the football?
>> Oh, super appealing, man. He's just he's
been great, you know, ever since college
and coming into the league. He's
immediately had success. So, just being
with a guy like that that can get you
the ball, you know, in different areas
of the field. I'm super excited. Super
excited to play, you know, with his
running ability and the way he opens up
the game and the way he just creates
space, you know, just by him being on
the field. Um, super excited about that.
Can't wait.
Washington has a really good tight end
room. John Bates, Ben Sinnet. Uh, what
did the team tell you on how they plan
to utilize you and maybe mesh all three
of you together?
>> Yeah, man. My job here really, man, to
come here and make make plays, be that
guy, speed, stretch the field, um, break
tackles, uh, catch the ball short, make
something out of nothing, um, catch a
ball on the flat, catch ball three
yards, get 15, and that's that's my role
here.
Liam,
>> hi Jake. We learned at about the same
time that you and your old Maryland
teammate Nick Cross were going to be
signing in Washington. Did you guys
communicate at all before you uh agreed
to deal?
>> Funny people, everyone keeps asking us
that, but um I had no idea my agent
called me after I signed. He was like,
"The got your boy." And I was like,
"Oh." He was like, "Nick." I was like,
"Oh, no way." So yeah, it's uh it's
really cool, you know, for me to us to
play again. Um play with each other
again. Obviously, we played in the same
division the past, you know, four years.
Been playing against him two times a
year, every year. So, it'll be cool to
play against him every day again.
>> Yeah. And and do you have a lot of
family in the area still?
>> What's it like to come back?
>> So, I'm actually not from here. Like,
I'm It's home because I went to school
here, but I'm from Georgia, though.
>> Gotcha. Thank you. Appreciate you.
>> Of course.
>> David.
>> Hey, Ch. Congratulations. Welcome back
to the DMV.
>> Thank you, brother.
>> Um David Harrison, WSA9. Obviously,
we'll meet in person later, but I want
to ask you your your career so far.
You've played with some older
quarterbacks, you've played with some
younger quarterbacks. Just kind of what
the biggest difference you've noticed
between the younger quarterbacks
compared to those older veterans that
you've played with.
>> Um, I'll say the obviously with the
veteran, it's just I feel like it's
always more streamlined. Like I think
back to like when I had uh Tanahill. Um,
is just like you can just feel the
poise, the veteran leadership, like
they're not trying to prove anything.
Um, with young guys, I feel like it's
more to prove. They got a more of a chip
on their shoulder. Um, I was that's
that's really it. Talent wise though,
man, I feel like any no matter what age
you are, if you got the talent, you you
can play. And so, I'm super excited,
man. I'm just super excited.
>> Yeah, absolutely. and and kind of
building off of another former team that
you're you're going to be rejoining,
Trail Burks here in Washington. What was
that relationship like with you guys in
Tennessee and and how are you looking
forward to getting back into an office
with him?
>> Super close with him. Um that's that's
one of my best friends, you know, back,
you know, when we were coming in, you
know, together. So, definitely called
him soon as as soon as I knew what was
going on and we were we were all we're
both super hype, you know, just talking
to each other. Uh that guy, man, he's
he's he's really a dog, bro. And I just
I can't wait to see him just fully show
everybody what he can do. Like I've seen
him when he's at full health, like full
confidence. Like that man can play
football and he's just not really got
the opportunity with with all the
injuries in the league, but I'm telling
y'all, bro, that dude is a beast. And
yeah, I'm super excited to get back with
him.
>> Thanks, Chick.
Donna.
>> Hey, Chick. Uh, welcome to Washington.
Uh, I heard that you're a big locker
room person and uh, meeting your two
teammates. What do you want them to know
about you as you enter the commander
locker room?
>> Hey man, I just want everyone to know
like we're going to have a good time,
man. I'm gonna be I'm I'm going to be
smiling every single day you know that
I'm here. Like you won't see me another
like one day not smiling. Um, just want
everyone to know, man. I'm Hey, let's do
this together, man. Everyone should be
super cool in the locker room. I heard
the locker room here is just is is a is
is like that. So, I'm super excited to
join the locker room with just
like-minded guys like me who um who
just, you know, just not a bad person.
Just in no way are they a bad person and
you just wake up every day, you just
want to go to work with them. Those are
the type I feel like that's what my
teammates should know about me. I'm a
guy that you would want to come to work
with every day for sure.
>> And could you talk a little bit about
culture and how big you are on culture
and what that means to you?
Yeah, culture is a huge thing for me,
man. Like, um, my past three years, I've
had so much shifting in and out. So, I'm
just really just want, you know,
stability and this place just has a good
culture, you know, going for it now.
Last year wasn't as much success, but,
um, the year prior, you know, a lot of
success and I've heard that the culture
never changed in the building. And
that's just really what I'm looking for
is stability regardless of winning,
losing. Um, are you who you say you are
every day? Like, are you what you preach
every day? And I feel like everyone here
is like that. and so much success to
come to this place.
>> Thank you,
>> Ben.
>> Hey, welcome uh to town. I'm just
curious obviously when you have as a as
a receiver, I'm sure you want to know
what's the plan, what's the what's the
scheme? How do you assess that when the
play caller is has not done this before
as a first time coordinator?
>> Um, so I can repeat can you repeat the
last part of the question? I just I
imagine that as a pass catcher, you kind
of want to know what system you're
walking into for offense. So with a guy
who's not called plays before, a first
time coordinator, how do you kind of
study that in advance to know kind of
what you're walking into?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. I mean, studying where
he's been, you know, his track record,
um, seeing the places he's been, seeing
the power of offense he's he's been in,
you know, he's already shown me that and
shown me a lot of, you know, clips from
from other days, places he's been like
Detroit, just watching all their clips
and seeing the offense that that they're
trying to bring over here. And I mean,
the way I see myself fitting in exactly
the roles that he showed me, like
everything, just watching guys with so
much space and just able to just use my
skill set, you know, to my advantage,
like fully to my advantage and just use
my speed, my quickness, like actually
run, you know, actually run real routes
on the field and be able to help the
quarterback, you know, be in the right
position, right place at the right time,
have good hands for him. And then I
think the thing about me, it's the Yak.
Y'all know about the Yak. Like I'm it's
like I can get the ball anywhere on the
field and make something happen. So
yeah.
>> Yeah. No, no, no, no doubt about it. Um
and just like I guess, you know, coming
back to to to have you already talked to
some of your uh Maryland people,
Lockxley, anybody like that?
>> You said, have I have I talked to them?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, no. I haven't talked to uh I haven't
talked to my Maryland folks. Not Not
yet. But yeah, I'm sure that'll come for
sure.
Blake,
>> hey, welcome uh to DTI. Welcome back to
the DMV. Yes,
>> sir.
>> Uh you know, you mentioned Yak and I was
going to talk to you about that.
Everyone knows that you're a playmaker
and you know, once you catch the ball,
you do get extended yards, but what
about your game would you say is
underrated that maybe people in DC don't
know that you're bringing to the area?
Um,
I would say
I'll say routes, man. Just like I feel
like over the past few years like
there's people trying to paint a
narrative, you know,
>> that more it's more just a yak guy. But
I can run any route on the route tree. I
just need to get the opportunity, you
know, to run the routes on the route
tree. And I think that'll be a thing
people be surprised about and they're
probably all thinking for the Yak, but
once they see that, that's one thing.
So, I talked to some folks and they were
like, "You played multiple positions
when you were in Tennessee." Like,
sometimes they had you moving in Hback
situations, different things like that.
So, how comfortable are you as far as
blocking, you know, if that's something
that you have to do?
>> You're saying from the Hback position
from where?
>> Yeah. Just or just moving around like if
you have to block, I mean, is that
something?
>> Yeah. That's also another that's also
another narrative that people, you know,
trying to paint um that blocking is
down, but it's not. I mean, PFF has
their own way of doing things. Like I,
like you said, I'm a lot of times in
those Hback positions. I don't put my
hand in the dirt much. So, I mean,
blocking has not been an issue for me.
Like, I'm gonna Y'all know I'm tough.
I'm gonna put my face on anybody. Like,
it's not an issue for me. And let's get
it.
>> Okay. All right. Welcome,
>> sir. Thank you.
>> All right. Appreciate Jig. Thanks.
>> Thank you guys. Appreciate y'all. I'll
catch y'all.
Recording stop.